[{"answer": "Tremendous workout", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Tremendous girl", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes, they do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A leg man? Why would I be a leg man? I don't need legs. I have legs. Have you ever seen her naked in the locker room", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't want to see her naked", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't want to see her naked", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well, that's your problem", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Look, you made the allegation. The least you could do is follow up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yes! Go in there! Do a little investigative journalism. I need to know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Wrong side", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "He can't go left", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, she was on his right side. He can't make a move with his left hand. Can't go left", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No! I'm lefty, can't go right. What about women? Do they go left or right", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Well, I know what they feel like", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You put her on a pedestal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "He puts 'em on a dental chair", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hey, does he ever talk about my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Oh, I know the type", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You touched 'em?", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yep! And, in two days, I'm off to that place", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yep! And, in two days, I'm off to that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Pffft", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Pffft", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "There's my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Talkin' to that woman", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "If that's my friend, she's talkin' to my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "If that's my friend, she's talkin' to my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well, I don't think they're real", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think they're real", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "If they're real, that's my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "If they're real, that's my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I gotta know, I'm talkin' to my friend. New scene", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I hear that's how she died", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Well, a lot of women are having them done", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Hi, Jer", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Oh...hi, my friend", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Oh. yeah. Alright.  So, where were we", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Implant.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Right, you were leaving", "qsentId": 42}]